<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Social Insight Tools</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Social Insight Tools</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pastry jelly cookie sugar donut orange</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/creator/design1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/creator/design1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Croissant orange croissant dolor orange croissant. Lollipop biscuit donut vanilla sweet croissant. Apple donut candy tiramisu cream jelly. Croissant sweet cookie vanilla tiramisu dolor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pastry jelly cookie sugar donut orange. Candy sweet cookie sweet donut marzipan. Vanilla cookie sprinkles pastry orange cookie. Marzipan donut ipsum sugar biscuit vanilla.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Candy cookie muffin pastry lollipop vanilla. Apple orange tiramisu jelly ipsum sugar. Candy cake orange ipsum orange muffin. Sugar pastry orange cream orange pastry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1. Social Algorithms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/social-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/social-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>We refer to this concept as Social Algorithms because they concern interactions between humans and evolve in concert with the knowledge of the community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>context mapping v1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tools/contexmaps_v1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tools/contexmaps_v1/</guid>
      <description>words</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrast &#43; Continuity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/contrast-continuity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/contrast-continuity/</guid>
      <description>two ingredients for human social cohesion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games That Matter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/games/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/games/</guid>
      <description>let&amp;rsquo;s play</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homepage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/_index2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/_index2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/01_homepage/convergence.png&#34; alt=&#34;Context Convergence&#34; style=&#34;display:block; margin-left:17%; width:auto; max-width:40%;&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Social Insight Tools&#xA;A blog and experimental space by markothell&#xA;Every group that &amp;ldquo;just clicks&amp;rdquo; is running the same program&#xA;You know the feeling. The meeting where everything flows. The workshop where strangers become collaborators. The moment when a group suddenly gets it together.&#xA;We call it chemistry, emergence, collective intelligence. But what if it&amp;rsquo;s more like electricity - a force that was always there, waiting for us to build the right tools to see it?&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m building tools to decode human coordination&#xA;Not personality tests. Not surveys. Interactive spaces where groups can see their own collective mind at work.&#xA;My first experiment: a tool that maps how communities think about prosperity. Users nominate ideas, vote on what to explore, then create a living map of their collective relationships. Everyone can explore the data, see the patterns, understand where alignment lives and where creative tension sparks.&#xA;[Try the prosperity mapping tool →]&#xA;Why this matters: Culture is eating software&#xA;We perfected version control for code. We created platforms where millions collaborate on open source projects. We can fork, merge, and evolve software at breathtaking speed.&#xA;Meanwhile, our social tools are stuck in the stone age. Surveys that extract data. Polls that flatten nuance. Platforms that feed on engagement instead of understanding.&#xA;What if communities could fork each other&amp;rsquo;s decision-making processes? What if the breakthrough your group had last Tuesday could be packaged, shared, and evolved by a thousand other groups? What if culture could iterate as fast as code?&#xA;The algorithm is already in you&#xA;Watch what happens when a group aligns:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Culture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/open-source-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/open-source-culture/</guid>
      <description>required</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/power/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/power/</guid>
      <description>power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Physics: Contrast, Context and Continuity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/social-physics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/social-physics/</guid>
      <description>required</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
