<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design Your Own Maps on Social Insight Tools</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design Your Own Maps on Social Insight Tools</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/drafts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/social-algorithm-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/social-algorithm-platform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-social-algorithm-platform&#34;&gt;A social algorithm platform&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Social Insight Tools (SIT) is an attempt to describe a cultural learning system comprised of experimental social activities; mini social apps connected by a common framework, evolving through  through open iteration and shared data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Activities are similar to parts of social media in that they are places for chatting, proposing ideas, surveying community members and listening in on the group’s conversation. A twitter poll is an activity. An online workshop is an activity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1. Social Algorithms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/social-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/social-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>We refer to this concept as Social Algorithms because they concern interactions between humans and evolve in concert with the knowledge of the community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conceptual Maps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/conceptual-maps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/conceptual-maps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emotional Intelligence Quadrants&#xA;These four quadrants of emotional intelligence consist of self-awareness, self-management, social awareness, and relationship management. Understanding and mastering these emotional intelligence quadrants is essential for improving personal and professional situations alike, enhancing one&amp;rsquo;s ability to regulate emotions, improve social interactions, and develop stronger relationships. SintellyLinkedIn&#xA;The axes are: Internal vs. External and Recognition vs. Regulation, creating four areas focused on emotional competency.&#xA;Attachment Style Grid&#xA;The upper left section is labeled secure. It is located between low avoidance and low anxiety. Secure attachment is marked by these two things: low relational avoidance and low relational anxiety. LindsaybramanNeurolaunch&#xA;This maps relationships along Attachment Anxiety vs. Attachment Avoidance axes, creating four relationship patterns:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fall in Love or The Limits of Social Algorithms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/how-to-fall-in-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/how-to-fall-in-love/</guid>
      <description>there are no limits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Culture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/open-source-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/open-source-culture/</guid>
      <description>required</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
